daytrippen.com 2015-12-21

# Daytrippen Privacy Policy Statement

Daytrippen.com is committed to the privacy of our visitors. We collect no personal information about you when you visit our Web site unless you choose to provide that information to us. Here is how we handle information about your visit to our Web site:

Information Collected and Stored Automatically: If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Web site, read pages or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store information like the following concerning your visit.

Your IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our Web site;  
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;  
The date and time you access our site;  
The pages you visit; and  
If you linked to our Web site from another Web site, the address of that Web site.  
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors—to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use.

Information That You Voluntarily Provide  
We do not collect personally-identifiable information unless you choose to provide it to us. If you provide us with personally identifiable information, for example by sending an e-mail or by filling out a form and submitting it through our Web site, we use that information only to respond to your message and to help us provide you with the information and services that you request  
  
Links to Other Sites  
This site may have links to the Web sites of other federal agencies. There may be links to private organizations, with their permission. Once you go to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. It is always a good idea to read the Privacy Policy of any Web site that you visit.

Cookies  
” Cookies” are small bits of text that are either used for the duration of a session (“session cookies”), or saved on a user’s hard drive in order to identify that user, or information about that user, the next time the user logs on to a Web site (“persistent cookies”). This Web site does not use persistent cookies or any other persistent tracking technology. One or more of our component sites may use session cookies to provide streamlined navigation. These session cookies are deleted from the component’s server after your session ends and information from them is not collected or saved.

Ad Servers  
To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and clickstream information.

Google Advertising

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.  
Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content [network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Affiliate Link Disclosure

Some links on this site are for products or tickets provide a small commission. This helps with costs associated with maintaining and running this site. NONE of the events or destinations links are paid or sponsored.

Editor’s Note: Comments that appear on the site are not the opinion of DayTrippen.com, but only of the comment writer. Personal attacks, offensive language and unsubstantiated allegations are not allowed.

For more information please contact us. [info@www.daytrippen.com](mailto:info@www.daytrippen.com)
